flashpoint-intel.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy – Flashpoint

We at EJ2 Communications, Inc. d/b/a Flashpoint (“Flashpoint,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) provided this privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) because we know that you care about how information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of Flashpoint when you access and use this website ([https://www.flashpoint-intel.com/](https://www.flashpoint-intel.com/)) (the “Website”) or access and use our proprietary software products (“Products”) via the Website. As of the Effective Date of this Privacy Policy, our Products include Flashpoint Platform, Reports, Curated Alerting and Analysis Assistance. Our Products may change from time to time.

By visiting our Website, or accessing and using our Products, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying [Terms of Service](https://www.flashpoint-intel.com/terms-of-service/). Access to and usage of our Products is also governed by the applicable software license agreement.

Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our [Terms of Service](https://www.flashpoint-intel.com/terms-of-service/).

**_General Data Protection Regulation (2016/679) (“GDPR”)_**

Flashpoint provides its Products on its customers\’ behalf as a “data processor,” as such term is defined under the GDPR. As such, customers are the data _controllers_ , as such term is defined under the GDPR, when using Flashpoint\’s Products. Thus, Customers must, as applicable, have an appropriate legal basis for its processing activities when using the Products, give appropriate notices under Articles 13-14, and fulfill all other data controller obligations under the GDPR.   

When serving as a processor, we have certain obligations under GDPR including only processing personal data at our customers\’ instructions reflected in the applicable software license agreement, providing assistance with fulfillment of rights requests, and implementing appropriate security for personal data. We will forward any inquiries, complaints, or requests received from data subjects with respect to use of the Products to the appropriate customer and await instructions before taking any action.

With respect to other processing activities, Flashpoint may act as a data controller. As examples, we are a controller with respect to certain activities related to prospective/current customers, customer end-users, and vendors (“Business Contacts”), and visitors to our Website, to the extent they are located in the European Economic Area (note that, in some cases, the categories may overlap such as Business Contacts using the Website). Please see below for more information related to such processing activities and other important information.

_Your Rights Under the GDPR_

As a natural person located in the European Economic Area, you have a right to: (i) request access to, correction and/or erasure of your personal data; (ii) object to processing of your personal data (such as direct marketing); (iii) restrict processing of your personal data; and (iv) request a copy of your personal data, or have a copy thereof sent to another controller, in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format under the right of data portability. You may exercise these rights and submit a GDPR complaint by contacting [gdpr-requests@flashpoint-intel.com](mailto:gdpr-requests@flashpoint-intel.com) with the subject line “ **GDPR**.” 

You also have the right to lodge a complaint about the processing of your personal data with an appropriate data protection authority, and, as applicable, to exercise third-party beneficiary rights under Flashpoint\’s Standard Contractual Clauses. 

Contact details for the EU data protection authorities can be found at: [http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm).

EU Representative  
EJ2 Communications Technology Ireland Limited, Inc. For any mailing, please send to:

70 Sir John Rogerson's Quay  
Dublin 2, Republic of Ireland  
Attention: GDPR  
Email: [gdpr-requests@flashpoint-intel.com](mailto:gdpr-requests@flashpoint-intel.com)

Flashpoint\’s intelligence portal may collect your IP address and this information will be used by Flashpoint for security purposes.

_Contact Information_

When you sign up to receive our newsletters or Product information on the Website, we collect your contact information. Contact information is provided via browser forms or online request forms, and includes: first name, last name, e-mail address, job title, name of the organization, country, state/region and phone numbers (fax, cell and/or landline). This contact information is used by our sales, support and Product teams to contact our visitors, customers and distributors for the purpose of providing the requested information, support, or Products. We do not collect any contact information from you when you use the Website unless you provide us with the contact information voluntarily.

_Analytics Services_

Like most organizations, we rely on automatic data collection technology, such as Google Analytics, New Relic, and Pardot when you visit our Website, or license, access, or use our Products online. These technology services may collect information on our behalf such as your IP Address, geolocation information, Internet service provider, browser type, operating system and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, date and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of the Website you visit, number of links you click while on the Website, search terms, and other data. This information is collected automatically and anonymized. The third parties we currently work with include the following (click on the links to view these organizations\’ privacy policies and find out more about what data they hold about you, what they do with it, and how to opt-out from certain data collection). Please be advised that if you opt out of any service, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Website.

For Google Analytics, please visit: [https://www.google.com/analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics)

For Pardot, please visit: [http://www.pardot.com/company/legal/privacy-policy/](http://www.pardot.com/company/legal/privacy-policy/)

For New Relic, please visit: [https://newrelic.com/termsandconditions/privacy](https://newrelic.com/termsandconditions/privacy)

_Cookies_

We use cookies to compile aggregate data as described above regarding our Website traffic which is used to improve our Website. Cookies are small packets of data that a website stores on your computer\’s hard drive so that your computer will “remember” information about your visits to our Website and other sites. Our cookie policy is available at [https://www.flashpoint-intel.com/cookie-policy/](https://www.flashpoint-intel.com/cookie-policy). If you do not want the Website to place a cookie on your hard drive, you may be able to turn that feature off on your device. Please consult your Internet browser\’s documentation for information on how to do this. However, if you decide not to accept cookies from our Website, the Website may not function properly.

_Aggregate Data_

In an ongoing effort to better understand our users and the Website, we might analyze your information in aggregate form to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Website. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our Products and the Website to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

_Additional Uses_

We also use contact information and other information collected pursuant to this Privacy Policy to respond to general inquiries, solicit feedback regarding our Website, Products and support, provide relevant content on our Website including advertisements regarding Products and third party products, and to communicate with you via email regarding our current and future Products.

_Business Transfers_

In the event of a merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar corporate event, or the sale of all or substantially all of our assets, we expect that the information that we have collected, including personal information, would be transferred to the surviving entity in a merger or the acquiring entity. All such transfers shall be subject to our commitments with respect to the privacy and confidentiality of such personal information as set forth in this privacy policy.

_Disclosure to Public Authorities_

We may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including for the purpose of meeting national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose personal information to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities or required by law or regulation including, but not limited to, in response to court orders and subpoenas.

_Opt-Out for Direct Marketing; Email Management_

You may opt out at any time from the use of your personal information for direct marketing purposes by contacting us at [privacy@flashpoint-intel.com](mailto:privacy@flashpoint-intel.com). Please allow us a reasonable time to process your request.

You may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “Manage Email Preferences” link located on the bottom of any Flashpoint marketing email and following the instructions found on the page to which the link takes you. You cannot opt out of receiving transactional e-mails related to their account or purchase orders.

_Retention of Personal Information_

We will retain your personal information in a form that identifies you only for as long as it serves the purpose(s) for which it was initially collected as stated in this privacy policy, or subsequently authorized. We may continue processing your personal information for longer periods, but only for the time and to the extent such processing reasonably serves the purposes of archiving in the public interest, journalism, literature and art, scientific or historical research and statistical analysis, and subject to the protection of this privacy policy. After such time periods have expired, we may either delete your personal information or retain it in a form such that it does not identify you personally.

_How We Protect Your Information_

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect the personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction, taking into account the risks involved in processing and the nature of such data, and comply with applicable laws and regulations. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet. In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Website may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.

_Children_

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through the Website or the Products. If you are under 13, please do not give us any personal information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children\’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide personal information through the Website or the Products without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

_Important Notice to Non-U.S. Residents_

Our servers are located in the US. If you are located outside of the US, please be aware that any information provided to us, including personal information, will be transferred from your country of origin to the US. Except in the case of data transfers under the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework, your decision to provide such data to us, or allow us to collect such data it through our Website or Products, constitutes your consent to this data transfer.

_Important Notice for Individuals of the European Economic Area and Switzerland_

Flashpoint complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from the European Union member countries (including Iceland, Liechtenstein and Norway) and Switzerland to the United States, respectively, pursuant to the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield. Flashpoint has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, Recourse, Enforcement and Liability (the “Privacy Shield Principles”). If there is a conflict between this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov/](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

Flashpoint is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission.

In compliance with the EU-US and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles, Flashpoint commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact Flashpoint at [privacy@flashpoint-intel.com](mailto:privacy@flashpoint-intel.com) with the subject line, “ **Privacy Shield**.” Flashpoint has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles to BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Flashpoint, please visit [http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint. If these processes do not result in a resolution, you may also contact your local data protection authority, the US Department of Commerce, and/or the Federal Trade Commission for assistance. Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.

_Onward Transfer to Third Parties under the Privacy Shield_

Like many businesses, we hire other companies to perform certain business-related services. We may disclose personal information to certain types of third party companies but only to the extent needed to enable them to provide such services. The types of companies that may receive personal information and their functions are: direct marketing assistance, lead generation services, order fulfillment, billing, customer service, data storage, hosting services, disaster recovery services, and sales support companies. All such third parties function as our agents, performing services at our instruction and on our behalf pursuant to contracts which require they provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by this privacy policy and implemented by Flashpoint. We may also disclose personal information to our affiliates in order to support marketing, sale and delivery of Products. 

In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

Flashpoint\’s accountability for personal data that it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party is described in the Privacy Shield Principles. In particular, Flashpoint remains responsible and liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if third-party agents that it engages to process the personal data on its behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless Flashpoint proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

_Opt-In and Opt-Out to Certain Onward Transfers under the Privacy Shield_ ****

Individuals have the opportunity to opt-out of sharing of their personal data with third parties other than our agents or before we use it for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized. To limit the use and disclosure of your personal information, please submit a written request to [privacy@flashpoint-intel.com](mailto:privacy@flashpoint-intel.com) with the subject line “ **Privacy Shield**.” 

We will not disclose your sensitive personal information to any third party without first obtaining your opt-in consent. In addition to any consent mechanisms on the Site, you may provide your consent by sending us an email at [privacy@flashpoint-intel.com](mailto:privacy@flashpoint-intel.com) with the subject line “ **Privacy Shield**.” In each instance, please allow us a reasonable time to process your response.

_Your Privacy Shield Rights_

Flashpoint acknowledges that EU and Swiss individuals have the right to access the personal information we maintain about them. Upon request to [privacy@flashpoint-intel.com](mailto:privacy@flashpoint-intel.com) with the subject line, “ **Privacy Shield** ,” we will provide you with confirmation as to whether we are processing your personal information, and have the data communicated to you within a reasonable time. You have the right to correct, amend or delete your personal information where it is inaccurate or has been processed in violation of this privacy policy. We may require payment of a non-excessive fee to defray our expenses in this regard. Please allow us a reasonable time to respond to your inquiries and requests.

_California Privacy Rights_

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to obtain certain information about the types of personal information that companies with whom they have an established business relationship (and that are not otherwise exempt) have shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year, including the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties. If you wish to submit a request pursuant to Section 1798.83, please contact Flashpoint via email at [privacy@flashpoint-intel.com](mailto:privacy@flashpoint-intel.com). In addition, Flashpoint does not monitor, recognize, or honor any opt-out or do not track mechanisms, including general web browser “Do Not Track” settings and/or signals.

_External Websites_

The Website and the Products may contain links to third-party websites. Flashpoint has no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of these websites. As such, we are not responsible for their content or privacy policies. You should check the applicable third-party privacy policy and terms of service when visiting any other websites, and before providing any personal information to such external sites.

_Changes to This Privacy Policy_

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any changes on the Website as soon as they go into effect. By accessing or using the Website after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

_How to Contact Us_

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or GDPR, please contact us in one of the following ways:

E-mail us at [privacy@flashpoint-intel.com](mailto:privacy@flashpoint-intel.com)

Or write to us at:  
EJ2 Communications, Inc.  
d/b/a Flashpoint  
111 East 14th St. #284  
New York, NY 10003  
Attention: Privacy

For GDPR Requests E-mail us at [gdpr-requests@flashpoint-intel.com](mailto:gdpr-requests@flashpoint-intel.com)

Or write to us at:  
EJ2 Communications Technology Ireland Limited, Inc.  
70 Sir Rogerson\’s Quay  
Dublin 2  
Republic of Ireland

For GDPR Data Processing Agreement Questions E-mail us at: [dataprocessingagreement@flashpoint-intel.com](mailto:dataprocessingagreement@flashpoint-intel.com)

Copyright 2018 EJ2 Communications, Inc. All rights reserved.
